conversocial.com 2018-03-27

# Conversocial - Social Customer Service | Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how we use and protect any information that you give Conversocial (UK) or Conversocial Inc. (together “Conversocial”) when you use this website. Conversocial is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Conversocial may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from the 17th March 2017.

### What we collect

We may collect the following information:

  * name and company information

  * contact information including email address

  * demographic information such as country, preferences and interests

  * Facebook or Twitter account identifiers and information, including data and communication history of Facebook pages that you administer

  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

### What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * To provide Conversocial's software services, including monitoring and responding to content on your Facebook pages and Twitter accounts.

  * Internal record keeping.

  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.

  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.

  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

### Sharing of information collected

We will limit disclosure of your Personal Information to any third parties as far as possible – and only disclose such information to third parties and for the purposes as provided for below.

Trusted Third Parties: we may employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and may need to share your information to facilitate our Services, including for analytics, hosting and to assist us with technical and administrative aspects of the Service (including credit card processing), and for general improvement of the Services.

Law Enforcement: to the extent permitted by applicable law, we may disclose information where it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities and to meet national security and law enforcement requirements (including cooperating with governmental authorities regarding the investigation of illegal activities), suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or as otherwise required by law.

Business Transfers: The only other scenarios in which we may otherwise share your Personal Information is if our company is substantially acquired by a third party, in which case your Personal Information may form part of that transfer.

### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

### Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

### Controlling your personal information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes

  * if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by [writing to us](mailto:support@conversocial.com).

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen. You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please [contact us](mailto:support@conversocial.com). If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

### Privacy Shield

Conversocial complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union to the United States. Conversocial has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>

### Disputes

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, Conversocial commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. EU individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Private Shield policy should first contact Conversocial at privacy@conversocial.com. If contacting us does not resolve your complaint, you may file a complaint, free of charge, with the [EU Data Protection Authorities (EU DPAs)](http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/article-29/structure/data-protection-authorities/index_en.htm).

Conversocial has further committed to cooperate with EU data protection authorities (DPAs) with regard to unresolved Privacy Shield complaints. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint from us, or if we have not addressed your complaint to your satisfaction, please contact the EU DPAs for more information or to file a complaint. The services of EU DPAs are provided at no cost to you.

### Binding Arbitration

Further, as explained in the [Privacy Shield Principles](https://www.commerce.gov/sites/commerce.gov/files/media/files/2016/eu_us_privacy_shield_full_text.pdf.pdf), a binding arbitration option will also be made available to you in order to address residual complaints not resolved by any other means.

### Enforcement

Conversocial is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission, Department of Transportation and any other US authorized statutory body.

In cases of onward transfer to third parties of data of EU individuals received pursuant to the EU-US Privacy Shield, Conversocial is potentially liable.

### Your Rights

You can contact the email address below to request access to the Personal Information we hold, subject to us validating your identity.You can also contact us if your Personal Information changes or if you no longer wish to be contacted regarding our Services.

To request access to your personal information, correct, update, or delete inaccurate data, or to file a privacy complaint, please email our Privacy Officer at: [privacy@conversocial.com](mailto:privacy@conversocial.com)
